

About me

I am a graphic designer looking for mu first industry job. I have worked as a freelance designer on several design projects including wedding invitations, event mailers, and charts.

Contact me or see my work

atalyart.com

contact@atalyart.com

ூ் 641-780-7332

Skills

Adobe Creative Suite - 2 years HTML 5 -2 years CSS 3 -2 years Microsoft Word - 2 years Power Point - 2 years Modern Hebrew - Fluent

Atalya Sigler Graphic Designer • Web Designer • Illustrator • Artist • Freelancer



Education

AAS Advertising & Graphic Design, 2023 Wake Technical Community College, Raleigh NC GPA 3.7

Wake Tech Community College: Web and Graphic Design Wake Tech Community College: Advanced Graphic Design Wake Tech Community College: Advertising and Graphic Design

Wake Tech Community College: Design Portfolio Wake Tech Community College: Design Basics



Certifications

Hubspot: Inbound Marketing Professional

Hubspot: Social Media Marketing



Work Experience

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER 2021-PRESENT

- · Manged two projects while attending school
- Communicated with clients during design Brief to produce high-quality deliverables

BATH & BODY WORKS - ASSOCIATE June 2020 - August 2021

- · Listened to customer needs build customer relationships
- Participated in sales at every stage of the in-store shopping experience
- · Led group of 7 cashiers during busy holiday sales
- Assisted a group of 5 individuals to unload, unbox, restock and build display tables

Achievements

• NCJAA ALL-ACADEMIC THIRD TEAM - 2022

This is an award given to student athletes that maintain GPA above 3.7 across two terms while playing on a collegiate team.

Torch Award Recipient- April 2023

The Torch Award is a honor that recognizes students who best exemplify the qualities of service, engagement, academics, and leadership. Winners are those who regularly go above and beyond in being a light in and outside of the classroom.

- Wake Tech Womens Soccer Captain 2022-2023
- National Career Development Association Conference competition - Third Place 2021